gosur.com 2018-11-01

# About Us - Gosur New York

**Gosur** was founded in 2006 with the idea of making more simple and interactive people’s experience around today’s traditional maps.  
With our website, it is easier than ever to get all the information that you need about a tourist destination. Booking a hotel room, discovering the best restaurants and attractions and getting detailed maps are some of the many possibilities that Gosur offers.

### Our Mission

 **Gosur** aims to be worldwide leaders in technological innovation, facilitating access to information for the global community.

By analyzing global trends, we store and process data in order to convert them in useful and relevant information for our users. With that purpose, we provide intuitive platforms, products and services of access to information with professional quality.

Operating in 11 different languages and with more than 30 million monthly visitors from all over the world, our community it’s growing faster than ever and it’s becoming one of the leading travel portals in the market.

With **Gosur** , it’s easier than ever to get all the information in just one place!

### Privacy Policy

As a general rule, this web site does not collect Personal Information about you when you visit the site. You can generally Visit this Site, without revealing, Personal Information, unless you choose to provide such information. Any Personal information collected shall NOT be shared with any other organization (public/private).

This site may contain links to other sites whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those sites.
